

Contact



914-343-3962



New City, NY 10956



mrandmrsfugazzotto@gmail.com

Profile

I was born in Hungary which is a tiny country in the heart of Europe bordered by the great Carpathian Mountains. I was growing up there and finished my schools in the capital city, Budapest.

High qualified customer service professional seeks work after years of exclusive brand retail experience. Strong understanding, administrating, time management and fast learning skills. With high moral standing and personal standing of integrity have a pleasant demeanor, work efficiency and high attention to details. Accuracy and ability to multitasking to perform the job more efficiently.

Amina Helga Fugazzotto

EDUCATION

Saint Margaret High School 2004 - 2008

Budapest College of Management

2010 - 2014

Business Administration and Management

Volunteer activity in the student union and participating on self-improvement courses.

Coordinate multiple college events during the semesters.

Offering information to visitors at open day and orientation day.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Nestle Nespresso – Customer Service Representative 2021–2021

Understanding and helping in costumers needs, evaluating promotions, selling products, and acknowledging people and strengthening the brand knowledge. I managed daily spreadsheets, payments, shipment, stock management opening and closing process with high settled safety and quality requirements. Efficient teamwork was as essential as self-judgment and time management,

TJX Companies - Cashier Jewelry associate 2020–2021

Engaging and assist customers, giving advice and helping them to find the product throughout the store or offering alternative options as needed. Coordinate drive-up merchandise pickups with other associates to keep salesfloor always desirable and up to date according to the seasonal changings. Offer excellent customer service by answering phone calls, accepting returns, and offering Company credit cards with joining benefits. Operate POS system to process customer purchases accurately and quickly, evaluate discounts and coupons as needed. Daily stock management and administrations of high value product safety checklist

Mercedes-Benz - Marketing assistant

2018-2020

Update and process spreadsheets, databases and marketing spending related expenses. Organizing important financial reports, bills and proofs with contracts and prepare TAX documents for the finance managers of the brand in every settlement quarter. Supporting marketing executives in organizing various projects and strengthening brand knowledge on the market. Searching for new platforms to promote brand and products. Collect the best value for money rate tender from partners. Lure potential customers and the same time strengthen the connection with existing clients.

Hobbies

Autodesk Sketchbook Databases Advertising Languages Travel

About Me

I am an open-minded cheerful outlook person.

I would love to acquire more knowledge-based ability, have more experience and finding happiness in the banking sector. I like to work hard, focusing on the job.

Organization and planning for me is a main skill in favor of high efficiency. I am a friendly and respectful collaborator who follows the orders and learn fast.

Nestle Nespresso – Customer Service Representative 2021–2021

Educate clients of the art of coffee tasting and help to develop their curiosity about the full range of products and the brand.

Operating daily by company rules and regulations and accomplish

Operating daily by company rules and regulations and accomplish personal and team monthly sales targets. My rules contain also high accuracy in cashiering at the cash register, keep money management and safety rules. Advanced MS office and Company's operation system knowledge was a key for my efficient daily operation. During these years I participated more self-improvement courses in cash management, time management, communication, customer care, problem solving and more. I am also ready to continue my learning process and enhance the range of my knowledge.

PERSONAL ACHIEVEMENTS

- Managing and Coordinate Plastic Aesthetic exhibition
 Representing Mercedes-Benz Automotive and acquire protentional costumers on the event. Coordinate the sales team and helping costumers to participate in the raffle game.
- Participating on Atelier event Representing Nestle Nespresso coordinating guests on the event and helping the exhibitors on their performing needs.

SKILLS

